mercy on call
you know anna there are procedures we
could look into to repair your eye
you're very kind but i'm comfortable
with who i am now
it's a good reminder ana i don't approve
of what you've done with my biotic
technology
i'm sorry you feel that way but it suits
my purposes now
ah you're here it's good to have backup
always glad to lend you a hand dr
ziegler
it's good to be working with you again
dr ziegler and under better
circumstances too
angela it's so strange to see you in
your armor
i could say the same for you
you seem there genji i am a different
man now
i am whole i got you some chocolates
genji
swiss they're the best thank you angela
perhaps you could share them with me
angela i have some chocolates for you
not swiss i suppose it will have to do
thank you gandhi angela
what did you wish for onya tanzaku if i
tell you
does it mean it won't come true this
reminds me of our time on base in
switzerland you are the only one who
stayed up so late
i enjoyed our conversations
lucio i never realized your father was
the one who invented vishka sonic
the cortex was his life's work owned and
patented by vishkar
but it's mine now
you know smoking's bad for your health
well
i have faith you can get me patched back
up doc
may you haven't aged a day what's your
secret
cryostasis but i'm not sure if i'd
recommend it
dr ziegler i don't think you've aged a
day since i last saw you
and neither have you mae
look at all the snow we should make snow
angels
why are you looking at me may
describing your work as unethical would
be a kindness
but the true question is whether or not
you can deny my discoveries
no i didn't think so
i know we have our differences but your
brilliant mind would be welcome amongst
my colleagues in oasis
no thank you you and your colleagues
discredit the field of science
i want nothing to do with it
keep the skies clear for me let's keep
the skies clear together
farah your mother always hoped you'd
follow in her footsteps
she did funny she never mentioned that
to me
pharah if your mother could see you now
i think she'd be proud of you
there's a first time for everything i
guess
what happened to you you tell me
dark
reinhardt don't you think it's time you
hung it up you're not getting any
younger
never i will fight to my last
breath reinhardt i don't approve of you
dragging that poor girl around on your
adventures
brigitte has made her choice i would
have her
at my side reinhardt
i don't approve of you dragging that
poor girl around on your adventures
brigitta has made her choice i would
have her at my side
reinhardt what are your plans for the
holidays i'll probably visit tobian's
family in gothenburg
like the last few years
doc i've been having diverse headaches
i've always said you should get your
head examined
tabion i miss ingrid's apple pie at the
holidays
well it just so happens she has some
saved for you
reinhardt i don't approve of you
dragging that poor girl around on your
adventures
angela you should know that no one could
stop brigitta from doing something she
had her mind set on
she's a lean home after all
tracer you should be careful we don't
know the side effects of using the
chronal accelerator
considering the alternatives i'm willing
to take the risks
vincent are you experiencing any issues
with your genetic therapy
other than a crippling addiction to
peanut butter
zenyatta i must admit i do not
understand how your healing works
and i do not understand much of how you
heal dr ziegler
i suppose we must all take some things
on faith
genji i was too late
i've got you brigitta taking care of you
brigitta
i'm taking care of you genji
reinhardt where would you be without me
i've got you tracer